Guide to the Records of the Deputy/Vice Chancellor for Academic Affairs, Eleazor Bromberg 1952-1980 RG 6.1 RG 6.1
New York University Archives
- Series I: Topical Files
  - Institute of Fine Arts, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Slavic Languages and Literature, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Urban Affairs, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - University Heights Council, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226312 2
  - Universities Research Assn., Inc, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - W., undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - GSAS, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Spanish and Portuguese, Dept. of, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Sotirivich, Wm. Vasilio GSAS, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Washington Square Council, 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Urban Affairs, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Union (65), undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - University Commission on Graduate Work, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - University Committee on Inventions and Patents, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Stridsberg, AB, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Libraries - Promotions, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - GPA - Promotions, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Promotions - GSSW, undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - UCAS - Promotions, undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - SCE - Promotions, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Graduate School of Business - Promotions, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - GSAS - Promotions, undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - School of Law - Promotions, undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - School of the Arts - Promotions, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - School of Engineering - Promotions, undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Washington Square, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Washington Square College - Promotions, undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Tenure Lists, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226313 0
  - Tenure, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Tenure, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Tenure Lists, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Tenure, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Tenure, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Tenure: General Information, Policy, Senate, Lists, etc., undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Tenure, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Trotta, Maurice, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Misc. Correspondence, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Club, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Handbook, undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Council, undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Records, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Records, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Federal Relations - Roth, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Financial Aid, undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Financial Aid, undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Founders' Day, undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - The Danforth Foundations, undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - The Ford Foundation, undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Kresge Foundation, undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - National Science Foundation, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - National Science Foundation, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Sloan Foundation, undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - G, undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - General Counsel - VP Miguel de Capriles, undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Gallatin, Albert Associates, undated (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - W.T. Golden, undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Goren, Arnold L. Assistant Chancellor, undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Committee on Graduate and Professional Education, undated (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - H., undated (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Hall of Fame, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Office of the President John C. Sawhill, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226314 8
  - Scholar Incentive Award, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Schirger, Joseph F., undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Albert Schweitzer Chair in the Humanities, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Security, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Sexton, Brendon, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Siam, undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Sonntag, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Spagnuolo, Mario (Medicine), undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Spanish and Portuguese, Dept. of, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Bosch, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Sponsored Programs, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Sponsored Programs Monthly Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - State Education Dept., 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Sponsored Research and Training Programs Manual, undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - State Education Dept., 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Student Affairs, undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Student Council (WSC), undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Student Press, undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Students, undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Stuart, William A. (FAS), undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - T., undated (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Town Hall, undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Travel Policy, undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Tenure Lists, undated (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Tenure, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Tenure, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Tuition Remission, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226315 5
  - Tuition Remission - SES Faculty, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - SES Tuition Remission - Remission Letters, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Saudek, Robert, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Registration Summaries, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Research, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Research Management Grant, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Research Policy, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Resumes, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - ROTC, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Ruttkowski, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - S., undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Safety, Center for, undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Salary Administration, undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Registration - Summary Reports, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Registrar, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Registrar, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Registration - Affairs, undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - HR 69, undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Privacy - Pell Act, undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Public Law 93-380, undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Publications Bureau, undated (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Purchasing, undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - R., undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Regional Council, undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Registration - Inter-School Data, undated (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Registration, undated (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - NYU Press, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - NYU Press, undated (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - NYU Report Material (Promotions and New Appointments), undated (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - NYU Spain, undated (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - O., undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Office Services, undated (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Officer's Group, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Office of the Controller, undated (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Office of Naval Research, undated (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - P., undated (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - (Faculty) Payroll, undated (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Placement Services, undated (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Presidential Search, undated (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Art Collection Proposals, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - NYU France, undated (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - NYU Press, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - School of the Arts, 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226316 3
  - School of the Arts, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Chrono - April, May, June, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Chrono - August through Decem., 1968 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Chrono - January, Feb., March, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Chrono - July, Aug., Sept., 1967 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - PIB - NYU Negotiations, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - PIB/NYU Negotiations (1), undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - PIB/NYU Negotiations (2), undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Polytechnical Institute of Brooklyn, NYU, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - University Htg. Sale, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Engineering & Science, School of, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - SES Tuition Remission - Remission Letters, undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - LOEB Student Center, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Ludlow, Gregory (FAS), undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - M., undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Mailing List, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Management Study Group, undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Marke Statement on HR 2223, undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Martin Luther King, JR Scholarship Fund, undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Mastrangelo, undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Meyer Physics Building, undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - S.M. Miller, undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Muehlig, John E., undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - N., undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - NACUBO, undated (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - NCHEMS, undated (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Neuman, Oscar (GPA), undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Neuschatz, Samuel (GSW), undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - NYU Mexico, undated (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Nulle, undated (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - NYU Art Collection, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - NYU Art Collection, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - School of Commerce, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226317 1
  - College of Dentistry, 1968-1970 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - School of Continuing Education, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - GPA, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - SCE - Faculty Meetings (Minutes), 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Schools - Business Administration, Graduate School of, 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - BPA - Faculty Meeting (Minutes) (Commerce), 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Continuing Education & Extension Services, School of, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - GBA, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - School of Education, 1968-1970 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Sc. Of Ed. - Faculty Council (Minutes), 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - GSAS, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - School of Engineering and Science, 1968-1970 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - GSAS, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Medical Center, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Medicine, School of, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226318 9
  - School of Law, 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Schools - Arts and Sciences, School of, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - School, Medicine, School of, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Graduate School of Social Work, 1968-1970 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Overage, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Education, School of, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Arts, School of the, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Athletics, Division of, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Commerce, Accounts and Finance, School of, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - J.T. Eco File, undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - All University Departments, 1959-1964 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Engineering & Science, School of, undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Dentistry, College of, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Personal Letters, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Personal, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227185 1
  - Philosophy, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Psychology, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - R, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Vice President for Public Affairs, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Provost, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Press Council, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - President's Task Force on Science Policy, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - President's Council GSAS, undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Registrar, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Politics, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Physics, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - SES Merger, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Davids, Douglas Prof - SES Letter of Appointment, undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - SES/PINY, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - SES Merger also see PIB/NYU, undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - SES, undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Engineering & Science, School of, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - SETE Project (SES), undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Harlem River Complex, undated (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Ragazzini, John R., undated (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Engineering, undated (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Li, Dr. Mo Chih (SES) Retiring 8/31/73, undated (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Toralballa, Leopoldo V., undated (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Zurcher, Arnold J. (FAS), undated (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Robert N. Boyd, undated (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Johnson, Lewis O. (SES), undated (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Robinton, undated (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Singer, Ferdinand, undated (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - W, undated (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Videotape Agreements, undated (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Van Norten, Roger, undated (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - V, undated (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Misc. Corr. W. other Univ., 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Senate, undated (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Misc. Correspondence w. other universities, etc 1974-75, undated (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Unemployment Insurance, undated (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - University Senate, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - University Senate, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Faculty Unionization, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227186 9
  - Unionization Elsewhere, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Union Election Lists, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - NRLB - also see UNION, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - NRLB - also see UNION, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Union - also see NRLB UNION, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Union/NLRB - also see FACULTY UNION, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Union/NLRB - also see FACULTY UNION, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Union, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Washington Sq. Coll. Promotions 13, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Division of Athletics - Promotions, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227187 7
  - School of Commerce - Promotions, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Dentistry - Promotions, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Promotions - FAS, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - School of Education - Promotions, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Sabbaticals - UCAS, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Sabbaticals - GBA, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Sabbaticals - Law School, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Sabbaticals - Sc. Of the Arts, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Sabbaticals - GSAS, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Sabbaticals - Courant, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Sabbaticals - School of Continuing Ed, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Sabbaticals - Medical Center, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Sabbaticals - Social Work, Graduate School of, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Sabbaticals - Commerce, School of, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Sabbaticals - Uni. College of Arts and Science, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Sabbatical Leaves - Dentistry, undated (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Sabbaticals - Education, School of, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Sabbaticals - GPA, undated (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Sabbaticals - Washington Square College, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Sabbaticals - Medicine, School of, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Sabbaticals - Engrng & Science, undated (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - GSAS Tenure, undated (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - GPA Tenure, undated (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - GBA Tenure, undated (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - DENT - Tenure, undated (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - COMMERCE - Tenure, undated (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - SCE - Tenure, undated (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - GSSW - Tenure, undated (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - ED - Tenure, undated (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Eng & Sci - Tenure, undated (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - MED - Tenure, undated (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - LAW - Tenure, undated (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - MED - RECS Sabb & Prom, undated (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - WSC Tenure, undated (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Anthropology, 1968-1971 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - UC - Tenure, undated (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Washington Square College, 1969-1970 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - FEES: All Schools, By Year, undated (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Board of Trustees: Minutes, General Correspondence, Supporting Papers 1939, 47, 62-64, 68, 72-75, 1939-1975 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227188 5
  - Miscellaneous: Faculty policy statements, HEW Questionnaire, Inactive status peo., Foreign Degrees General Correspondence, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Inquiries and Requests: Academic Years 1962-63 thru 1969-70, 1962-1970 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Applied Science (Ferri), 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Applied Science, 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Annual Payroll Encumbrance Report, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - AAUP - American Association of University Professors, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - American Geographical Society, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - American Council on Education, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - American Civil Liberties Union, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Federation, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Ales, Victor W. (GSW), undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Advanced Technology Labs (Ferri), 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Admissions, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Administrative Management Council, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Academic Planning Office of, undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - A., undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Library, undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Milton Lipson, undated (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Tamiment Library, undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Libraries, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Libraries (General), undated (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Libraries, 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Lewin, Seymour, undated (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Lewin, Arie, undated (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Leahy, David G. (Classics), undated (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Levy, Dr. Dorothy, undated (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - La Maison Francaise, undated (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Department of Labor - Wage and Labor Division (Childs), undated (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Department of Labor - Wage and Labor Division (ED), undated (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Dept of Labor (Wilonsky), undated (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - L, undated (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Klibbe, Lawrence H. (UCAS), undated (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - KOPCKE - IFA, undated (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Koenigil, Mark, undated (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Kirkman, Robert G., undated (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Kirby, JC - VP and General Counsel, undated (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Kelejian, Harry, undated (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Karp, Samuel M., undated (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Internal Revenue Service, undated (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - K, undated (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Insurance, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227189 3
  - Institutional Research, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Institutional Facilities - VP John O'Mara, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Institutional Facilities - VP John O'Mara, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Institute of Judicial Administration, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - ICD, undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - ID Cards, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - ID Cards, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Information Associates, Inc, undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - IBM Training Manual - Magnetic Tape Selectric Typew., undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Hester, James M - President, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Hindle, Brooke, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Hook, Sidney, undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Hester, James M - President, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - H.E.O.P, undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - H.E.O.P., undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - H.E.O.P., undated (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Hall of Fame, undated (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Hamilton, Charles V., undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Harrison, Hershel, undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Hatchett, John, undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Hebrew Technical Institute, undated (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Hegis, undated (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Assistant Chancellor - Contract Officer - CE Enroth, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Nadiri, M. Ishaq (Economics), undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Georgiadis, Hourmouzis G. (Economics), undated (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Petratos (Economics), undated (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Edel, Leon (GSAS), undated (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Named or Endowed Professorships (NYU), undated (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - EDUCOM Interuniversity Communications Council, Inc., undated (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Asst. Chancellor, Contract Officer, CE Enroth, 1975-1976 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Director, Computing Center, undated (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Directory, undated (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Draft - see file stock room, undated (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - De Grazia, Alfred - Also See: University of the New World, undated (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Development, Office of, undated (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Development, undated (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - De la Solana, Alberto Gutierrez, undated (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Degree Programs, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227190 1
  - Death Benefits, undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Dean's Council, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Dean's Council, 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Data Processing Center, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - D, undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - CUNY, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Cutler, undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Cartter, Allan M., undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Clifton, Budd and Burke, undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - C.O.P.E.S., undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Copyright Policy, undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - By-Laws, undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Byrnes, Joseph A. - Assistant Secretary of the University, undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - CAI, undated (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Carnegie Council, undated (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Center for Interdisciplinary Programs - Official Material, undated (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Center for Interdisciplinary Programs - General, undated (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Center for Interdisciplinary Studies (Ferri), 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Bursar, undated (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Burnell, Louis, undated (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Bursar, undated (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Bobst Library, undated (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Booz, Allen & Hamilton Inc., undated (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Borowitz, Sidney - Chancellor, undated (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Breil, Giora, undated (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Brody, undated (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Battle, Turner III, undated (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Beidelman, Thomas O. (GSAS), undated (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Bela Bartok Archives, undated (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Birnbaum, Allan (CIMS), undated (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Delois Blakeley, undated (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Applied Sci - People, undated (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - NYU's Association Memberships, undated (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Association of American Colleges, undated (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Assoc. of American Universities, undated (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Association of Colleges and Universities, undated (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - B, undated (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Baker, George W. (NSF), undated (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Banks, Hugh C - Assistant Chancellor, undated (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Frederick P. Bargebuhr, undated (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Barish, undated (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Baumol, William (Economics), undated (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Barney Building, undated (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Basic Time Sharing, undated (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Applied Science Program (Ferri), undated (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Washington Square Council Meeting, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227191 9
  - Physics, 1969-1970 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - UCAR, undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Non-Faculty Personnel (Gitlow, Collins), undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Committee on the Effective Use of Faculty Resources (Cartter), undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Data Processing, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Officers' Group, 1969-1970 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Outside Activities, 1969-1970 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Outstanding Achievements, undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Overage, undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - P, undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Page Charge, undated (Box 28, Folder 12)